Angelica Romero

Angelica.Romero.crhs@gmail.com 615-506-4291

Professional Summary

Attentive and professional Concierge with over 10 years in customer facing roles looking to add a positive impact to your company and customers by providing above and beyond service. I have extensive experience processing requests, responding promptly and with discretion to meet diverse needs. Excellent listener with an organized approach and reliable personality.

Experience

Accounting Clerk
Dimension Hospitality

Feb 2021 to Current Nashville, TN

- Handle cash, charge and account payments to settle guest bills.
- Review and respond chargebacks monthly, while keeping chargeback log current.
- · Verify deposits of each cashier and document variances daily.
- Reconcile disputed rooms, invoice for open balances, close out open guest folio's.
- Assist with month-end reconciliations.
- · Verify weekly cash drops and input records into profitsword
- Submit credit card deposits into profitsword, and upload bank deposits to corporate along with daily revenue detail report.
- Use Bill to input, code and approve vendor invoices daily.

Procurement Buyer Loews Hotels & Co May 2019 - Apr 2020 Nashville, TN

- Negotiated pricing, delivery schedules and discount terms with suppliers for short- and longterm product needs.
- Worked with contract representatives to resolve problems with delivery timelines and performance.
- Established and maintained professional relationships with suppliers, resulting in fewer supply chain delays and better operations flow.
- Maintained, prepared and reviewed price lists, purchasing files and reports.
- Verified accuracy of suppliers' bills against original purchase orders to avoid billing errors.

Accounts Receivable Clerk Loews Hotels & Co

Jan 2017- Apr 2019 Nashville, TN

Maintained billing files, payments received and pending payment files.

- Investigated and resolved discrepancies during the account reconciliation process.
- Generated and shared reports with management on pending payments, accounting and statements involving weekly aging reports and month-end closing reports.
- Communicated with vendors and tenants to facilitate collection of payment for past due accounts.

Education

Associate of Applied Science, Electrical Engineering Nashville State Community College

Aug 2021 -May 2024 Nashville, TN

Bachelor of Electrical Engineering Tennessee Tech University August 2024 – Current

Languages

Fluent : English, Spanish. Intermediate: Portuguese

Skills

Interpersonal Skills: Conflict Resolution, Attention to Detail, Leadership in Team-Based

Environments.

Programming Languages: C++, R.